[
    {
        "question": "Who's the Leek master?",
        "c1": "Rethaz",
        "c2": "Dandelion",
        "c3": "Vinthir",
        "c4": "Swim",
        "answer": "Burza"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which streamer uploads cancer tier decks the second a new patch arrives?",
        "c1": "Mogwai",
        "c2": "JJPasak",
        "c3": "Merchant",
        "c4": "SirPumpkn",
        "answer": "Swim"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"A grave error\"",
        "c1": "Radovid",
        "c2": "Geralt",
        "c3": "Eredin",
        "c4": "Emhyr",
        "answer": "Ciri"
    },
    {
        "question": "There's been a mistake, he's no mage.",
        "c1": "Vicovaro Medic",
        "c2": "Abaya",
        "c3": "Avallach",
        "c4": "Dorregaray",
        "answer": "Alchemist"
    },
    {
        "question": "RADOVID",
        "c1": "ASIA",
        "c2": "EUROPA",
        "c3": "AMERICA",
        "c4": "ANTARCTICA",
        "answer": "AFRICA"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Ciri cards are there?",
        "c1": 0,
        "c2": 1,
        "c3": 2,
        "c4": 4,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Uma is...",
        "c1": "Just a monster",
        "c2": "Ciri",
        "c3": "Geralt",
        "answer": "Avallach"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"DANCE OF DEATH!\"",
        "c1": "Wardancer",
        "c2": "Elven scout",
        "c3": "Elven swordmaster",
        "c4": "Elven Bomber",
        "answer": "Blue Mountain Elite"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many factions are in the game?",
        "c1": 4,
        "c2": 2,
        "c3": 3,
        "c4": 6,
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the row limit?",
        "c1": 12,
        "c2": 9,
        "c3": 11,
        "c4": 8,
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Yennefer cards are there?",
        "c1": 1,
        "c2": 2,
        "c3": 4,
        "c4": 5,
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Triss cards are there in the game?",
        "c1": 1,
        "c2": 3,
        "c3": 5,
        "c4": 0,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "One of these isn't in the game",
        "c1": "G: Igni",
        "c2": "G: Yrden",
        "c3": "G: Aard",
        "c4": "Geralt",
        "answer": "G: Axii"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Myrgtabrakke do?",
        "c1": "Deal 3 damage, then 1.",
        "c2": "Deal 1 damage 4 times",
        "c3": "Damage units by 2, 2 and then 1",
        "c4": "Damage units by 2, 1 and then 1",
        "answer": "Deal 2 damage 3 times"
    },
    {
        "question": "Slave Hunter",
        "c1": "Charm a unit with 3 power or less",
        "c2": "Create a Bronze unit from your opponents starting deck",
        "c3": "Spawn a base copy of this unit on your other rows",
        "c4": "Reset a unit",
        "answer": "Charm a Bronze with 3 power or less"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Zoltan cards are there?",
        "c1": 0,
        "c2": 1,
        "c3": 3,
        "c4": 4,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many gold cards does NG have?",
        "c1": 17,
        "c2": 15,
        "c3": 21,
        "c4": 13,
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "The faction with the least amount of golds is...",
        "c1": "Nilfgaard",
        "c2": "Monsters",
        "c3": "Scoia'tael",
        "c4": "Northern Realms",
        "answer": "ST, NR and SK have the same amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "The faction with the most golds is",
        "c1": "MO",
        "c2": "NR",
        "c3": "ST",
        "c4": "SK",
        "answer": "NG"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yennefer: Enchantress",
        "c1": "Spawn Unicorn or Chironex",
        "c2": "Deal 1 damage to the Highest enemies",
        "c3": "Deal 5 damage",
        "c4": "Boost the lowest allies by 1",
        "answer": "Spawn the last Bronze or silver Spell you played"
    },
    {
        "question": "The faction with the least amount of silvers is",
        "c1": "Nilfgaard",
        "c2": "Monsters",
        "c3": "Scoia'tael",
        "c4": "Northern Realms",
        "answer": "Skellige"
    },
    {
        "question": "The faction with the most bronzes is",
        "c1": "Skellige",
        "c2": "Scoia'tael",
        "c3": "Northern Realms",
        "c4": "Nilfgaard",
        "answer": "Monsters"
    },
    {
        "question": "The faction with the least amount of bronzes is",
        "c1": "Skellige",
        "c2": "Monsters",
        "c3": "Northern Realms",
        "c4": "Nilfgaard",
        "answer": "Scoia'tael"
    },
    {
        "question": "Milva",
        "c1": "Return each player's Highest unit to their deck and boost yours by 3",
        "c2": "Truce: return the Highest Ally and Enemy to each players' hand.",
        "c3": "Reset the Highest units on each side of the board.",
        "c4": "Swap 2 cards",
        "answer": "Return each player's Highest Bronze or Silver unit to their deck"
    },
    {
        "question": "A king should be merciless towards his enemies and generous to his friends.",
        "c1": "Francesca",
        "c2": "Henselt",
        "c3": "Bran",
        "c4": "Foltest",
        "answer": "Radovid"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hazards are there in the game?",
        "c1": 4,
        "c2": 5,
        "c3": 6,
        "c4": 7,
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "How many boons are there in the game?",
        "c1": 1,
        "c2": 4,
        "c3": 5,
        "c4": 3,
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Spores",
        "c1": "Reset a unit and weaken it by 3",
        "c2": "Reset a unit and strengthen it by 3",
        "c3": "Deal 13 damage",
        "c4": "Reset a unit and weaken it by 6",
        "answer": "Deal 2 damage to all units on a row and clear a boon from it"
    },
    {
        "question": "The summer sun reflected in the quiet waters of the Alba - that´s Nilfgaard to me",
        "c1": "Tibor",
        "c2": "Jan Calveit",
        "c3": "Emhyr",
        "c4": "Menno",
        "answer": "GOD EMPEROR MORVRAN KAST"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mogwai is a main ____ player.",
        "c1": "Monsters",
        "c2": "Skellige",
        "c3": "Scoia'tael",
        "c4": "Northern Realms",
        "answer": "Nilfgaard"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Create cards are there?",
        "c1": 4,
        "c2": 7,
        "c3": 12,
        "c4": 8,
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "Aguara: True form can't pull:",
        "c1": "Scorch",
        "c2": "Alzur's Thunder",
        "c3": "Necromancy",
        "c4": "Rockslide",
        "answer": "Marching Orders"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of these is not like the others.",
        "c1": "Ornamental Sword",
        "c2": "Mahakam Horn",
        "c3": "Ointment",
        "c4": "Dimeritium Shackles",
        "answer": "Commander's Horn"
    },
    {
        "question": "Monsters' runestone is:",
        "c1": "Stribog",
        "c2": "Zoria",
        "c3": "Dazhbog",
        "c4": "Morana",
        "answer": "Devana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nilfgaard runestone is:",
        "c1": "Stribog",
        "c2": "Zoria",
        "c3": "Devana",
        "c4": "Morana",
        "answer": "Dazhbog"
    },
    {
        "question": "Skellige's runestone is:",
        "c1": "Dazhbog",
        "c2": "Zoria",
        "c3": "Devana",
        "c4": "Morana",
        "answer": "Stribog"
    },
    {
        "question": "Northern Realms' runestone is:",
        "c1": "Stribog",
        "c2": "Dazhbog",
        "c3": "Devana",
        "c4": "Morana",
        "answer": "Zoria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Scoiatael's runestone is:",
        "c1": "Stribog",
        "c2": "Zoria",
        "c3": "Devana",
        "c4": "Dazhbog",
        "answer": "Morana"
    },
    {
        "question": "King or beggar, what´s the difference? One dh´oine less",
        "c1": "Toruviel",
        "c2": "Isengrim",
        "c3": "Aelirenn",
        "c4": "Schirrú",
        "answer": "Iorveth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lamia",
        "c1": "Spawn Rain, Clear Skies or Arachas Venom",
        "c2": "Spawn Rain, Clear Skies or Arachas Behemoth",
        "c3": "Consume all units in your graveyard and boost by 1 for each",
        "c4": "Lock a unit.",
        "answer": "Deal 4 damage, if under Blood Moon, deal 7."
    },
    {
        "question": "Geralt: Igni has a minimum cap of:",
        "c1": 24,
        "c2": 22,
        "c3": 20,
        "c4": 21,
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "Eskel: ",
        "c1": "Swordmaster",
        "c2": "Mentor",
        "c3": "Wolf",
        "c4": "Beast Slayer",
        "answer": "Pathfinder"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lambert:",
        "c1": "Beast Slayer",
        "c2": "Mentor",
        "c3": "Pathfinder",
        "c4": "Scoundrel",
        "answer": "Swordmaster"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vesemir:",
        "c1": "Wolf",
        "c2": "Swordmaster",
        "c3": "Beast Slayer",
        "c4": "Pathfinder",
        "answer": "Mentor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Thunderbolt",
        "c1": "Boost up to 6 random allies by 2",
        "c2": "Boost 3 adjacent units by 2 and give them 3 armor",
        "c4": "Deal 2 damage to up to 6 random enemies",
        "answer": "Boost 3 adjacent units by 3 and give them 2 armor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Swallow Potion",
        "c1": "Deal 2 damage to up to 6 random enemies",
        "c2": "Boost up to 6 random allies by 2",
        "c3": "Boost 3 adjacent units by 3",
        "c4": "Boost a unit by 8",
        "answer": "Boost a unit by 10"
    },
    {
        "question": "Petri's Philter",
        "c1": "Boost a unit by 10",
        "c2": "Boost 3 adjacent units by 3 and give them 2 armor",
        "c4": "Deal 2 damage to up to 6 random enemies",
        "answer": "Boost up to 6 random allies by 2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dorregaray can't pull:",
        "c1": "Wyvern",
        "c2": "Ocvist",
        "c3": "Slyzard",
        "c4": "Panther",
        "answer": "Barbegazi"
    }
]
